A Guide to the Charles James Apperley [Nimrod] Papers 1797-1851
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Volume Eleven 1816-1839, 96 items mounted on 75 pages
  Mr. Bass to Editor of The Sporting Magazine page 50
  W.L. Castell to Henry Crawter page 28
  William Chambers to C.J. Apperley page 14
  N. Copland to Mary Ann Pittman pages 53
  Vincent Corbet to Gray Inn Coffee House page 15
  Henry Crawter to Mary Ann Pittman pages 60, 63
  Henry Crawter to Mr. Porter page 32
  Henry Crawter to Proprietors of The County Chronicle pages 17, 18
  John Crowder to Henry Crawter page 16
  "Dashwood" [N. Copeland] to D.N. Shuey page 37
  Harry Dobre to William Young page 20
  G.V. Driver to Henry Crawter page 21
  E. Dunn to James Pittman page 42
  James Dunn to Frederick W. Pittman page 67
  H. Fleming to Henry Crawter page 27
  Mr. Haines to Mary Ann Pittman page 63
  "The Hermit in London" to D.N. Shuey page 48
  Henry Hewes to Mr. Payne page 23
  Charles Howe to Mary Ann Pittman page 42
  Jack's Coffee House to Mary Ann Pittman page 33
  William Lake to Mrs. Mary Ann Pittman page 26
  L. Lambert to Dear Sir page 41
  Rev. G.L. Langdon to Henry Crawter page 34
  "Luck Penny" [Francis Beirne] to D.N. Shuey pages 43, 44, 45, 47
  Frederick W. Pittman (son of John & Mary Ann Pittman) to James Dunn pages 64, 65, 66, 69, 70, 71, 72, 73, 74, 75
  John Pittman to C.J. Apperley pages 8, 11
  John Pittman to "Vagiana" pages 9, 10
  Horatio Ross to Mary Ann Pittman page 35, 36
  Hugh Rowland to Henry Crawter pages 19, 22
  Archer Ryland to Henry Crawter page 24
  Godfrey Sykes, Solicitor of Stamps, to Mrs. Mary Ann Pittman page 25
  Theatre Royal Covent Garden to D.N. Shuey page 39
  Tompson's lawyers to Henry Crawter page 29
  "Vagiana" to John Pittman page 6
  "Verex" to Editor of The Sporting Magazine page 54
  John Wheble to John Pittman pages 2, 3, 4, 5
  W.B. Wheeler to Henry Crawter page 31
  Benjamin Wingrove to Henry Crawter page 30
  "The Young Forester" to Mary Ann Pittman page 41
  [?] to John Pittman page 12
  Subjects in volume 11:
  account of John Pittman with Butler & Teague page 7
  account of John Wheble with W. Walter page 1
  American interested in sports pages 65, 66
  Collin Drummond [Riparius] page 47
  Lord Harley, death of page 20
  law suit against Delano page 57
  life insurance policy receipts pages 40, 46
  Nimrod pages 9, 10, 12, 35, 36, 37, 60
  George Palmer page 49
  John Pittman, death of pages 17, 18
  Shropshire fox hounds page 49
  E. Tattersall, death of (1810) page 63
  R. Tattersall, death of (1795) page 63
  Colonel Wyndham's hounds page 37
  VOLUME TWELVE
- Volume Twelve ca. 1818, 1829-1830, 16 items
  Volume twelve consist of 16 legal documents pertaining to law suits Wheble v. Smith and Pittman v. Young, and a statement of debts due to the executors of Mr. Pittman, ca. 1818, and 1829-1830. Mr. William Young was the former editor of The Sporting Magazine.